This is my impersonation of the Martin Luther King that you all quote, we want black people to shut up.
It is me, Martin Luther King Jr., the only civil rights leader who ever lived.
I had a dream and it came true.
So the rest of you Negroes can leave it alone now.
Why are you protesting in the street?
I would have never inconvenienced those nice white people like that.
They're just trying to get to work.
It is actually against the law for any black person to say something that contradicts anything that I said.
So if you hear it, tell them I'm disappointed in them and that it is illegal to say that.
Everybody loves me now, just like everybody loved me back then.
It's why I died of natural causes at the age of 98.
I only gave one speech.
Don't Google it.
I'm sure the person who has quoted me to you would have supported me back then as well.
Just ask their parents or their grandparents what they thought about me.